dqindia.com 2017-06-10

# Privacy Policy - CIOL

**Privacy Statement for Cyber Media India Limited**

Thank you for visiting our web site. This privacy policy tells you how we use personal information collected at ciol.com. Please read this privacy policy before using the site or submitting any personal information. By using ciol.com, you are accepting the practices described in this privacy policy. These practices may be changed, but any changes will be posted and changes will only apply to activities and information on a going forward, not retroactive basis. You are encouraged to review the privacy policy whenever you visit ciol.com to make sure that you understand how any personal information you provide will be used.

**Note:** the privacy practices set forth in this privacy policy are for ciol.com only. Sometimes this site contains links to other sites whose information practices may be different than ours. Visitors should consult the other sites’ privacy notices, as we have no control over information that is submitted to, or collected by, these third parties.

**Collection of Information**

We collect personally identifiable information, like names, postal addresses, email addresses, etc., when voluntarily submitted by our visitors. This information you provide will only be used to fulfill your specific request, unless you give us permission to use it in another manner, for example to add you to one of our mailing lists.

CIOL.com sometimes may offer content (e.g., contests, promotions) that is sponsored by or cobranded with identified third parties. By virtue of these relationships, the third parties may obtain personally identifiable information that you voluntarily submit to participate in the site activity. CIOL has no control over these third parties’ use of this information. CIOL site will notify you at the time of requesting personally identifiable information if these third parties will obtain such information.

**Control use of your Personal Information**  
We give you choices and control over the collection and use of your Personal Information. You can update your Personal Information or remove your email address from our email list.

There are known methods that spammers can use to hide their identity by using other people’s email address to send out emails. If you have any question about the genuineness of an email you receive that appears to be from CIOL, contact us at webmaster@cybermedia.co.in and do not furnish personal information in response to that email.

**Cookie Technology**  
The Site may use cookie and tracking technology depending on the features offered. CIOL’s usage of cookie is very rare except when you opt for “Remember my ID on this computer”. Personal information cannot be collected via cookies, however, if you previously provided personally identifiable information, cookies may be tied to such information. Aggregate cookie and tracking information may be shared with third parties.

**Distribution of Information**  
We may share information with governmental agencies or other companies assisting us in fraud prevention or investigation. We may do so when: (1) permitted or required by law; or, (2) trying to protect against or prevent actual or potential fraud or unauthorized transactions; or, (3) investigating fraud which has already taken place. The information is not provided to these companies for marketing purposes.

**Commitment to Data Security**  
Your personally identifiable information is kept secure. We have put in place appropriate physical, electronic, and managerial procedures to safeguard and help prevent unauthorized access, maintain data security, and correctly use the information we collect online. All emails and newsletters from this site allow you to opt out of further mailings.

**Copyright notice, disclaimer and terms of use**

CyberMedia India Online (CIOL.com) is an Information Technology-related service which has been created to be easily accessible to all users, but it has limitations and risks which must be made known to the users before participating. By using the Service Users are consenting and agreeing to abide by these terms. CIOL will not be held liable for any losses, damages, costs or expenses arising from user’s reliance on the accuracy of the content supplied /provided on ciol.com. CIOL reserves the right to change, cancel or introduce new terms and conditions in the Agreement in its discretion at any time, and without prior notice. Users are advised to go thru the terms and conditions before using this service. Usage of the Service by the User shall be deemed as an agreement to the new Terms and Conditions.  
Click here for details on terms and conditions.

**Privacy Contact Information**  
If you have any questions, concerns, or comments about our privacy policy you may contact us using the information below:

**By Post:**

CyberMedia India Ltd,  
205, Shree Complex,  
73, St. Johns Road,  
Bangalore 560042.  
India

**By e-mail:**

webmaster@cybermedia.co.in

We reserve the right to make changes to this policy. Any changes to this policy will be posted.
